Robert Hupka Collection of Toscanini Test Pressings and Dom Baron Chant Recordings
Robert Hupka Collection of Toscanini Test Pressings
- Toscanini recordings
  - Hérodiade - Vision fugitive - Massenet, [06/28]/1905; hupka_1987; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Hidden Wounds, Like the Rosebud - [Frank LaForge], 11/26/1906; hupka_3977; Serial # C-4065; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - The hills o' Skye - Victor Harris, lyricist - William McLennan, 4/26/1911; hupka_3929; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Hofballtänze, op. 161 - Joseph Lanner, hupka_3275; BLR-5968-2; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Holberg Suite - Grieg; Symphony No. 4 - Sibelius; Les Eolides - Franck; La Valse - Ravel, 4/27/1940; hupka_2413; 050076-1; Part 3 [Note - Pieces listed under "title" are from the 04.27.1940 concert - It is unknown which tracks are on this item]; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Holberg Suite - Grieg; Symphony No. 4 - Sibelius; Les Eolides - Franck; La Valse - Ravel, 4/27/1940; hupka_2414; 050077-1; Part 4 [Note - Pieces listed under "title" are from the 04.27.1940 concert - It is unknown which tracks are on this item]; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Holberg Suite - Grieg; Symphony No. 4 - Sibelius; Les Eolides - Franck; La Valse - Ravel, 4/27/1940; hupka_2415; 050078-1; Part 5 [Note - Pieces listed under "title" are from the 04.27.1940 concert - It is unknown which tracks are on this item]; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Holberg Suite - Grieg; Symphony No. 4 - Sibelius; Les Eolides - Franck; La Valse - Ravel, 4/27/1940; hupka_2418; 050076-1; Part 3 [Note - Pieces listed under "title" are from the 04.27.1940 concert - It is unknown which tracks are on this item]; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Holberg Suite - Grieg; Symphony No. 4 - Sibelius; Les Eolides - Franck; La Valse - Ravel, 4/27/1940; hupka_2419; 050077-1 [Note - Pieces listed under "title" are from the 04.27.1940 concert - It is unknown which tracks are on this item]; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Holberg Suite - Grieg; Symphony No. 4 - Sibelius; Les Eolides - Franck; La Valse - Ravel, 4/27/1940; hupka_2422; 050077-1; Part 4 [Note - Pieces listed under "title" are from the 04.27.1940 concert - It is unknown which tracks are on this item]; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Holberg Suite - Grieg; Symphony No. 4 - Sibelius; Les Eolides - Franck; La Valse - Ravel, 4/27/1940; hupka_2423; 050078-1 [Note - Pieces listed under "title" are from the 04.27.1940 concert - It is unknown which tracks are on this item]; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Holberg Suite - Grieg; Symphony No. 4 - Sibelius; Les Eolides - Franck; La Valse - Ravel, 4/27/1940; hupka_2424; 050078-1; Part 5 [Note - Pieces listed under "title" are from the 04.27.1940 concert - It is unknown which tracks are on this item]; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Holberg Suite - Grieg; Symphony No. 4 - Sibelius; Les Eolides - Franck; La Valse - Ravel, 4/27/1940; hupka_2425; 050079-1A [Note - Pieces listed under "title" are from the 04.27.1940 concert - It is unknown which tracks are on this item]; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Holberg Suite - Grieg; Symphony No. 4 - Sibelius; Les Eolides - Franck; La Valse - Ravel, 4/27/1940; hupka_2426; 050080-1A [Note - Pieces listed under "title" are from the 04.27.1940 concert - It is unknown which tracks are on this item]; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Holberg Suite - Grieg; Symphony No. 4 - Sibelius; Les Eolides - Franck; La Valse - Ravel, 4/27/1940; hupka_2427; Part 7 [Note - Pieces listed under "title" are from the 04.27.1940 concert - It is unknown which tracks are on this item]; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Holberg Suite - Grieg; Symphony No. 4 - Sibelius; Les Eolides - Franck; La Valse - Ravel, 4/27/1940; hupka_2428; 050074-1; Part 1 [Note - Pieces listed under "title" are from the 04.27.1940 concert - It is unknown which tracks are on this item]; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Holberg Suite - Grieg; Symphony No. 4 - Sibelius; Les Eolides - Franck; La Valse - Ravel, 4/27/1940; hupka_2429; 050075-1; Part 2 [Note - Pieces listed under "title" are from the 04.27.1940 concert - It is unknown which tracks are on this item]; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Holberg Suite - Grieg; Symphony No. 4 - Sibelius; Les Eolides - Franck; La Valse - Ravel, 4/27/1940; hupka_2438; 050074-1A [Note - Pieces listed under "title" are from the 04.27.1940 concert - It is unknown which tracks are on this item]; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Holberg Suite - Grieg; Symphony No. 4 - Sibelius; Les Eolides - Franck; La Valse - Ravel, 4/27/1940; hupka_2439; 050074-1; Part 1 [Note - Pieces listed under "title" are from the 04.27.1940 concert - It is unknown which tracks are on this item]; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Holberg Suite - Grieg; Symphony No. 4 - Sibelius; Les Eolides - Franck; La Valse - Ravel, 4/27/1940; hupka_2440; 050075-1A [Note - Pieces listed under "title" are from the 04.27.1940 concert - It is unknown which tracks are on this item]; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Holberg Suite - Grieg; Symphony No. 4 - Sibelius; Les Eolides - Franck; La Valse - Ravel, 4/27/1940; hupka_2441; 050075-1; Part 2 [Note - Pieces listed under "title" are from the 04.27.1940 concert - It is unknown which tracks are on this item]; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Holberg Suite - Grieg; Symphony No. 4 - Sibelius; Les Eolides - Franck; La Valse - Ravel, 4/27/1940; hupka_2442; 050076-1A [Note - Pieces listed under "title" are from the 04.27.1940 concert - It is unknown which tracks are on this item]; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Holberg Suite - Grieg; Symphony No. 4 in A minor, op. 63- Sibelius; Les Eolides - Franck; La Valse - Ravel, 4/27/1940; hupka_2907; Part 3; 050076-1; Tracks on item come from this broadcast, but do not include all titles listed; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Holberg Suite - Grieg; Symphony No. 4 in A minor, op. 63- Sibelius; Les Eolides - Franck; La Valse - Ravel, 4/27/1940; hupka_2908; Part 3; 050076-1; Tracks on item come from this broadcast, but do not include all titles listed; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Holberg Suite - Grieg; Symphony No. 4 in A minor, op. 63- Sibelius; Les Eolides - Franck; La Valse - Ravel, 4/27/1940; hupka_2915; Part 5; 050078-1; Tracks on item come from this broadcast, but do not include all titles listed; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Holberg Suite - Grieg; Symphony No. 4 in A minor, op. 63- Sibelius; Les Eolides - Franck; La Valse - Ravel, 4/27/1940; hupka_2916; Part 5; 050078-1; Tracks on item come from this broadcast, but do not include all titles listed; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Holberg Suite - Grieg; Symphony No. 4 in A minor, op. 63- Sibelius; Les Eolides - Franck; La Valse - Ravel, 4/27/1940; hupka_2917; Part 4; 050077-1; Tracks on item come from this broadcast, but do not include all titles listed; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Holberg Suite - Grieg; Symphony No. 4 in A minor, op. 63- Sibelius; Les Eolides - Franck; La Valse - Ravel, 4/27/1940; hupka_2918; Part 5; 050078-1; Tracks on item come from this broadcast, but do not include all titles listed; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Holberg Suite, op. 40 - Grieg, 05/17/1940 [?]; hupka_2144; 050806-2R; Shellac disc
  - Holberg Suite, op. 40 - Grieg, 5/17/1941 [?]; hupka_2156; 050805-2R; Shellac disc
  - Holberg Suite, op. 40 - Grieg, 05/17/1941 [?]; hupka_2168; 050804-2R; Shellac disc
  - Holberg Suite, op. 40 - Grieg, 05/17/1940 [?]; hupka_2202; 050807-2R; Shellac disc
  - Huguenots - Bianca al par di neve alpina - Meyerbeer, 2/27/1905; hupka_3692; w/piano; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Huguenots - Bianca al par di neve alpina - Meyerbeer, 11/7/1909; hupka_3693; 6005-B; w/orchestra; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - I Due Foscari - O vecchio cor, che batti - Verdi, 4/14/1913; hupka_1110; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - I hear you calling me - Charles Marshall, lyricist - Harold Harford, 6/16/1921; hupka_1167; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - I hear you calling me - Charles Marshall, lyricist - Harold Harford, 10/12/1927; hupka_1289; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - I Lombardi - Polonaise - Verdi, 3/18/1909; hupka_1128; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - I Pagliacci - Aitolo, Signor! - Ruggiero Leoncavallo, hupka_3766; 92011; No. 10; Shellac disc
  - I Pagliacci - Bird Song - Ruggiero Leoncavallo, 1911; hupka_1193; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - I Pagliacci - Bird Song - Ruggiero Leoncavallo, hupka_3932; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - I Pagliacci - Decidi il mio destin - Ruggiero Leoncavallo (Pt. 1), circa 1930-1939; hupka_3923; CK-2010-2; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - I Pagliacci - No, Pagliacco non son! - Ruggiero Leoncavallo, hupka_3768; 92012; No. 15; Shellac disc
  - I Pagliacci - No, pin non m'ami! - Ruggiero Leoncavallo (Pt. 2), circa 1930-1939; hupka_3924; CK-2011-2; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - I Pagliacci - No, pin non m'ami! - Ruggiero Leoncavallo (Pt. 2), circa 1930-1939; hupka_3925; CK-2011-2; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - I Pagliacci - Prologo - Si può? Signori... Un nido di memorie - Ruggiero Leoncavallo, 11/23/1905; hupka_1989; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - I Pagliacci - Prologo - Si può? Signori... Un nido di memorie - Ruggiero Leoncavallo, [04/18]/1905; hupka_1990; Cat # 85081; Shellac disc
  - I Pagliacci - Un nido di memorie - Ruggero Leoncavallo, hupka_0858; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - I Pagliacci - Vesti la giubba - Ruggiero Leoncavallo, circa 1937-1949; hupka_1938; 2SB-2400-2; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - I Pagliacci - Vesti la giubba - Ruggiero Leoncavallo, hupka_3767; 1210-C; No. 11; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - I Pagliacci - Vesti la giubba - Ruggiero Leoncavallo, circa 1930-1939; hupka_3879; CO-4758-2TI; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - I Pagliacci - Vesti la giubba - Ruggiero Leoncavallo, 10/18/1907; hupka_1151; Shellac disc
  - I Pescatori de Perle [Les pêcheurs de perles] - Brahma, gran Dio - Bizet, 3/18/1911; hupka_3832; 3423-F2; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - I Pescatori de Perle [Les pêcheurs de perles] - Brahma, gran Dio - Bizet, 3/18/1911; hupka_3835; 3423-F2; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - I Pescatori de Perle [Les pêcheurs de perles] - Del tempio al limitar - Bizet, 3/24/1907; hupka_3669; 8036-A; Shellac disc
  - I Pescatori de Perle [Les pêcheurs de perles] - Siccome un di caduto il sole - Bizet, 3/18/1911; hupka_3836; 3102-F; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - I Pescatori di Perle [Les pêcheurs de perles] - Del tempio al limitar - Bizet, hupka_3420; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - I Pescatori di Perle [Les pêcheurs de perles] - Mi par d'udir - Bizet, 12/11/1912; hupka_3444; 923-B; Shellac disc
  - I Puritani - [Il rival salvar tu dei...] Suoni la tromba - Vincenzo Bellini, 1907; hupka_3254; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - I Puritani - A te o cara amor talora - Bellini, 1/6/1928; hupka_1917; 7226-A; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - I Puritani - Ah! Per sempre - Bellini, 12/13/1907; hupka_1874; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - I Puritani - Ah! Per sempre io ti perdei - Bellini, hupka_2028; 276-AJ; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - I Puritani - Ah! Per sempre io ti perdei - Bellini, hupka_2029; 276-AJ; Shellac disc
  - I Puritani - Ah! Per sempre io ti pendei - Vincenzo Bellini, hupka_3487; 276-AJ; Shellac disc
  - I Puritani - Bel sogno beato di pace - Vincenzo Bellini, hupka_3486; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - I Puritani - Cinta di fiori - Donizetti, 12/17/1924; hupka_3897; CK-1817-2; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - I Puritani - Qui la voce - Vincenzo Bellini, hupka_0924; IRCC-50-A; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - I Puritani - Suoni la tromba - Bellini, 3/6/1907; hupka_1143; Cat # 88500; Shellac disc
  - I Puritani - Vien dilatto - Bellini, 3/18/1911; hupka_3837; IRCC-116-B; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - I Puritani - Vieni, vieni fra queste braccia - Vincenzo Bellini, hupka_4010; Spelled "Galvani" on item; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - I Vespri Siciliani - O patria... o tu, Palermo - Verdi, 2/17/1927; hupka_4115; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - I Vespri siciliani [Les vêpres siciliennes] - O tu Palermo - Verdi, circa 1907-1918; hupka_3811; Serial # 74207; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - I Vespri Siciliani [Vèpres siciliennes. Merci jeunes amies] [Merci, compagnons] - Verdi, [04/13/1905]; hupka_0850; IRCC-8-B; 64029; B-424; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - I Wonder as I Wander, 1956; hupka_2039; Shellac disc
  - Iberia - Mvt. I - Debussy (conclusion), 2/11/1945; hupka_2567; Record # D5-RC-99-1; Shellac disc
  - Iberia - Mvt. I - Debussy (Part 1), 2/11/1945; hupka_2480; Record # D5-RC-98-1A; Studio 8-H; Shellac disc
  - Iberia - Mvt. I - Debussy (Part 1), 2/11/1945; hupka_2494; Record # D5-RC-98-1A; Studio 8-H; Shellac disc
  - Iberia - Mvt. I - Debussy (Part 1), 2/11/1945; hupka_2555; Record # D5-RC-98-1; Studio 8-H; not released; Shellac disc
  - Iberia - Mvt. II - Debussy (conclusion), 2/11/1945; hupka_2591; Record # D5-RC-101-1; Shellac disc
  - Iberia - Mvt. II - Debussy (Part 1), 2/11/1945; hupka_2579; Record # D5-RC-100-1; Shelf # is written as T-246, but should probably be T-247; Shellac disc
  - Iberia - Mvt. III - Debussy, 2/11/1945; hupka_2506; Record # D5-RC-102-1; Studio 8-H; Shellac disc
  - Iberia - Mvt. III - Debussy, 2/11/1945; hupka_2603; Record # D5-RC-102-1; Shellac disc
  - Ich grolle nicht - Schumann, 5/5/1911; hupka_3810; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Ich grolle nicht, op. 48/7 - Robert Schumann, hupka_3295; BB-19308-2; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Ich liebe dich - Beethoven; Panis Angelicus - Franck; Lungi dal caro bene - Guiseppe Sarti; Batti, batti, O bel Masetto - Mozart; Clair de Lune - Debussy, hupka_2163; VinylDisc
  - Ideale - F. Paolo Tosti, 12/30/1906; hupka_3694; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Ideale - F. Paolo Tosti, 11/23/1915; hupka_3695; 6019-B; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Ideale - Paolo Tosti, circa 1903-1908; hupka_1252; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Il barbiere di Siviglia - Dunque io son - Rossini, hupka_0845; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Il barbiere di Siviglia - La ran la le ra... Largo al factotum - Rossini, 1907; hupka_0842; Serial # 6405-A; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Il barbiere di Siviglia - La ran la le ra... Largo al factotum - Rossini, 4/19/1920; hupka_0843; Serial # 6263-A; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Il barbiere di Siviglia - La ran la le ra... Largo al factotum - Rossini, 4/19/1920; hupka_0844; Serial # 6263-A; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Il Barbiere di Siviglia - O il meglio mi scordavo... Numero quindici - Rossini, hupka_1235; Serial # IRCC-96-B; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Il Barbière di Siviglia - Se il mio nome - Rossini, circa 1903-1908; hupka_1204; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Il Barbiere di Siviglia - Una voce poco fa - Rossini, hupka_3226; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Il Guarany - C'era una volta - Antônio Carlos Gomes, 5/11/1908; hupka_1893; 74170; Shellac disc
  - Il Guarany - Sento una forza indomita - Antônio Carlos Gomes, 1917; hupka_1339; Bolis is listed on item, but he was deceased when item was said to be recorded; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Il re pastore - L'amerò sarò constante - Mozart, 10/12/1913; hupka_0963; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Il Segreto di Susanna - Oh la nube leggera - Ermanno Wolf-Ferrari, 2/19/1913; hupka_3941; 6-12924; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Il Seraglio - [Die Entführung aus dem Serail] - Che pur aspro l'ouore - Mozart, 5/30/1913; hupka_1197; Serial # 719-M; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Il Signor Bruschino - Overture - Rossini, hupka_1667; Serial # D5-RC-496-2A; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Il Signor Buschino - Overture - Rossini, 11/11/1945; hupka_1317; 637-B; VinylDisc
  - Il Signor Buschino - Overture - Rossini, 11/11/1945; hupka_1318; 637-B; VinylDisc
  - Il Trovatore - Miserere - Verdi, 12/27/1909; hupka_3672; C 8506; Shellac disc
  - Il Trovatore - Abbietta zingara - Verdi, Apr. 1930; hupka_4111; Serial # 59746-2; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Il Trovatore - Abbietta zingara - Verdi, Apr. 1930; hupka_4112; Serial # 59746-2; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Il Trovatore - Act II - Scene and Aria - Verdi, hupka_3505; 066766-1A; Shellac disc
  - Il Trovatore - Ah si, ben mio coll'essere - Verdi, circa 1908-1910; hupka_0872; Serial # 317-A1; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Il Trovatore - Ah! Si, ben mio - Verdi, [04/12]/1907; hupka_1041; Serial # HRS-1001-A; Shellac disc
  - Il Trovatore - Deserto sulla terra - Verdi, 10/22/1907; hupka_1692; Serial # B-4891; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Il Trovatore - Di due figli vivea padre beato - Verdi, hupka_4108; Serial # CE-1277-2; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Il Trovatore - Di due figli vivea padre beato - Verdi, 7/10/1923; hupka_4109; Serial # CE-1277-2; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Il Trovatore - Di due figli vivea padre beato - Verdi, 7/10/1923; hupka_4110; Serial # CE-1277-2; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Il Trovatore - Di quella pira - Verdi, circa 1908-1910; hupka_0875; Serial # 92032; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Il Trovatore - Il balen - Verdi, [04/15/1908]; hupka_1048; Serial # C-6114; Shellac disc
  - Il Trovatore - Il balen - Verdi, 3/8/1909; hupka_1049; Serial # C-6866; Shellac disc
  - Il Trovatore - Il Balen - Verdi, 3/5/1929; hupka_1192; Serial # 191620-6; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Il Trovatore - Il balen del suo sorriso - Verdi, [11/27/1912]; hupka_2898; Serial # 936-A; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Il Trovatore - Miserere - Verdi, circa 1908-1910; hupka_0876; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Il Trovatore - Per un ora - Verdi, 1908; hupka_2910; Serial # HRS-2015-B; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Il Trovatore - Stride la vampa - Verdi, 10/8/1906; hupka_1233; Shellac disc
  - Il Trovatore - Stride la vampa - Verdi, hupka_4020; Serial # 3803-F; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Il Trovatore - Stride la vampa - Verdi, hupka_4021; Serial # 3803-F; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Il Trovatore - Stride la vampa - Verdi, hupka_4022; Serial # 3803-F; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Il Trovatore - Tacea la notte - Verdi, hupka_1956; IRCC-142-B; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Il Trovatore - Tacea la notte - Verdi, 5/15/1908; hupka_3820; C-6198; 74116; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Il Trovatore - Tacea la notte - Verdi, circa 1930-1939; hupka_3926; 6770-B; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Il Trovatore - Tacea la notte - Verdi, 9/13/1923; hupka_3994; Serial # C-28469; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Il Trovatore - Tacea la notte - Verdi, 9/13/1923; hupka_3995; Serial # A-28469; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Il Trovatore - Tacea la notte placida - Verdi, 7/27/1906; hupka_2008; Cat # 74058; Shellac disc
  - Il Trovatore - Timoz di me & D'amor sull' ali rosee - Verdi, 9/16/1924; hupka_3996; Serial # A-30297; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Im tiefen Keller sitz ich hier - [Karl L. Fischer, lyricist - Carl Muchler], [10/19/1903]; hupka_3484; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Im wunderschönen Monat Mai, op. 48, No. 1 and Ich grolle nicht, op. 48, No. 7 - Robert Schumann, [10/16/1903]; hupka_3482; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Images - Ibéria, L. 122 - Mvt. I - Debussy (Pt. 1), 11/18/1941; hupka_1482; Shellac disc
  - Images - Ibéria, L. 122 - Mvt. I - Debussy (Pt. 2), 11/18/1941; hupka_1485; Shellac disc
  - Images - Ibéria, L. 122 - Mvt. I - Debussy (Pt. 2), 11/18/1941; hupka_1486; Shellac disc
  - Images - Ibéria, L. 122 - Mvt. II - Debussy (Pt. 1), 11/18/1941; hupka_1487; Shellac disc
  - Images - Ibéria, L. 122 - Mvt. II - Debussy (Pt. 2), 11/18/1941; hupka_1488; Shellac disc
  - Images - Ibéria, L. 122 - Mvt. III - Debussy (complete mvt.), 11/18/1941; hupka_1489; Shellac disc
  - Images - Ibéria, L. 122; Prelude to the Afternoon of a Faun, L. 86; La Mer, L. 109 - Debussy, 2/7/1946; hupka_2681; Rehearsal; Part 9 [Note - Pieces listed under "title" are from the 02/7/1946 rehearsal - it is unknown which tracks are on this item]; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Improvisations at the Organ, hupka_2173; Location: Newport, RI; VinylDisc
  - In Sweet September - Hope-Temple (?), hupka_1246; Serial # HO-1809-AF; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Incantatrice (Vocal Waltz) - Luigi Arditi, hupka_4001; Serial # 6414-B; Spelled "Galvani" on item; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Inno delle Nazioni - Verdi, lyricist - Arrigo Boito, hupka_3087; Taken from the O.W.I. film track; Parts 1 & 2; Shellac disc
  - Inno delle Nazioni - Verdi, lyricist - Arrigo Boito, hupka_3088; Taken from the O.W.I. film track; Part 3; Shellac disc
  - Intermezzi Goldoniani - Marco Enrico Bossi; Jota Aragonesa - Mikhail Glinka Sides 3 & 5, 9/3/1944; hupka_2974; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [Invano] - Serenata - Paolo Tosti, [04/12]/1907; hupka_1778; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Invitation to the Dance - Weber, 3/12/1949; hupka_2644; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Iris - Apri la tua finestra - Pietro Mascagni, hupka_4114; 1461-B; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Je t'aime - Massenet [author - Suzanne Bozzani], [10/28/1912]; hupka_1142; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Jewels of the Madonna - T'eri un giorno - Ermanno Wolf-Ferrari, 7/1/1912; hupka_1245; Serial # HO-201-AF; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - The Jewels of the Madonna - Apri, lo bella, la feuestrella - Ermanno Wolf-Ferrari, hupka_3438; HO 202-AF; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - The Jewels of the Madonna [I gioielli della Madonna] - Sono un demonio buono - Ermanno Wolf-Ferrari, hupka_2850; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - The Jewels of the Madonna [I gioielli della Madonna] - Sono un demonio buono - Ermanno Wolf-Ferrari, hupka_2922; Serial # HO-116; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Jolie fille de Perth - Quand la flamme de l'amour - Bizet, 1/28/1910; hupka_1178; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Joseph - Champs Paternels - Etienne Nicholas Méhul, 10/23/1917; hupka_1265; Shellac disc
  - Joseph - Champs Paternels - Etienne Nicholas Méhul, 10/23/1917; hupka_1266; Serial # 20898-A; Shellac disc
  - Jota Argonesa - Mikhail Glinka (conc.); Hungarian Dance No. 1 - Brahms, hupka_1316; 593-B; D5-TC-1526-1; VinylDisc
  - Jota Argonesa - Mikhail Glinka (Part 1), hupka_1315; 593-A; D5-TC-1514-1; VinylDisc
  - L' elisir d'amore - Chiedi all'aura lusinghiera - Gaetano Donizetti, 1907; hupka_3999; Serial # 551-I; Spelled "Galvani" on item; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - L' elisir d'amore - Chiedi all'aura lusinghiera - Gaetano Donizetti, 1907; hupka_4000; Serial # 551-I; Spelled "Galvani" on item; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - L'Africana - Adamastor - Meyerbeer, circa 1903-1905; hupka_1974; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - L'Africana - Adamastor, re dell'onde profonde - Meyerbeer, [4/16/1914]; hupka_1107; Shellac disc
  - L'Africana - Adamastor, re dell'onde profonde - Meyerbeer (L'Africaine - Adamastor, roi des vagues profondes), 3/23/1911; hupka_4095; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - L'Africana - Adamastor, roi des vagues profondes - Meyerbeer, 11/23/1903; hupka_1984; IRCC-86-B; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - L'Africana - Adamastor, roi des vagues profondes - Meyerbeer, 1905; hupka_1985; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - L'Africana - Averla tanto amata - Meyerbeer, hupka_1138; Serial # 2156-AF; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - L'Africana - Figlia di Regi - Meyerbeer, hupka_1134; Serial # 214-AF; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - L'Africana - Figlia di Regi - Meyerbeer, hupka_1135; Serial # 214-AF; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - L'Africana - Figlia di Regi - Meyerbeer, hupka_1136; Serial # 214-AF; Shellac disc
  - L'Africana - Figlia di Regi - Meyerbeer, hupka_3439; HO 205-6F; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - L'Africana - Figlia di Regi - Meyerbeer (L'Africaine - Fille des rois?), circa 1910-1911; hupka_4093; Serial # HO-205-AF; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - L'Africana - Figlia di Regi - Meyerbeer (L'Africaine - Fille des rois?), circa 1910-1911; hupka_4094; Serial # HO-205-6F; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - L'Africana - Gia l'odio - Meyerbeer, circa 1906-1917; hupka_1948; IRCC-142-A; Shellac disc
  - L'Africana - O Paradiso - Meyerbeer, circa 1908-1910; hupka_0865; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - L'Africana - O Paradiso - Meyerbeer, circa 1918; hupka_1907; 2W-2532-2; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - L'Africana - Quando amor mi accende - Meyerbeer, hupka_1137; Serial # 215-AF; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - L'Allegro, il Pensieroso ed il Moderato - Sweet Bird - Handel, hupka_0940; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - L'amico Fritz - Duetto delle ciliegel - Pietro Mascagni, 1/14/1924; hupka_1959; HRS-1039-A; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - L'Assedio di Corinto - Overture - Rossini (Part 1), hupka_1679; Unpublished; Record # D5-RC-508-2; Shellac disc
  - L'Assedio di Corinto - Overture - Rossini (Part 2), hupka_1691; Unpublished; Record # D5-RC-509-2A; Shellac disc